Hi there, I'm Jace Blackburn, founder and
CEO of GoSteady and I'm going to show
you how to set up your device in less than
90 seconds.
All right, so for the first step for
installing your GoSteady, you're going to
loosen this knob on the side of the clamp a
few times until you have some good
flex in here.
Next, we're going to find where we want to
mount this on the walker.
We're going to go ahead and mount on the
right side just beneath the hand grip.
So, first things first, make sure you move
the brake cable out of the way.
You don't want to clamp that.
Then bring the clamp over the top and give
it a few turns.
We don't need to go fully snug yet, as
we're going to next flip this
up. Give the button one press here.
You'll start to see some blue lights
flashing.
And then finally, we're going to go ahead
and scan this QR code to do a few
steps on the phone before we finish setup.
We're going to go scan our QR code here.
Go ahead and get started.
The only fields required here are going to
be your
name and phone number.
Email is optional as another way of signing
in,
but this is all really text-based
in terms of passwords and resets.
So we'll continue here.
Give it one second as it gets set up.
We'll be getting a login code for messages.
Just verify that. And
we're all set up.
Alright, and in order to finish up, just
turn this down, give this a few
turns until it's nice and snug, and you're
ready to roll.
Enjoy!